GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
(GROANS)
SOFIA: We could've had
a good thing, you and I.
(GUNSHOT)
- You!
- Yeah.
Me.
When I get out of
here, I'm gonna confess.
My connection
with Sofia. All of it.
No, you wanna pay
your debt, you live with it.
It's what the city needs.
RA'S: When I brought
you back to life,
I asked you to be my
eyes and ears in Gotham.
You became so much more.
- Let her go, now.
- No!
- I'll never go with you.
(SCREAMS)
You killed her!
BRUCE: So, now,
you're gonna return it?
What am I supposed to say?
"I stole your jewelry. Sorry."
Sometimes, that's enough.
Can you do it?
TABITHA: Migraine still?
BARBARA: It's like I've been
hit in the head with a brick.
(BARBARA BREATHES HEAVILY)
PENGUIN: You
could escape anytime.
You're planning something.
Something spectacular.
But, when we're done,
the world out there,
that'll be the asylum.
(CHUCKLES)
(BUZZING)
("FOOL FOR YOU"
PLAYING ON WALKMAN)
Get back in your bunk, Tetch.
(INAUDIBLE)
Don't even try hypnotizing me. I
can't hear a word you're saying.
I'm not talking to you!
- I'm talking to her.
- (GASPS)
Jeez. Tortuga. You almost
gave me a heart attack.
Wait. Where the hell
are your headphones?
(CHOKES)
Did I do it right?
Right as rain, in
the plain in Spain.
Knock, knock, called the cock.
Time to rise and wield your scythe.
CRANE: I fear I will require
a moment more, Mr. Tetch.
Our moment is fleeting,
my dear Mr. Crane.
Its wings desperately beating.
(SIZZLING)
There, now, scarcely
a drop spilled.
Shall we, Mr. Tetch?
Let us be at pains, Mr. Crane.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(ALARM BLARING)
When I say "three hairs
past a freckle," gentlemen,
I do not mean five hairs past.
Let's do better next time, hmm?
Mind both P's and Q's, Valeska.
We are not your militia
to be becked and called.
I dread to think where
you'd be without us.
Boys, boys, let's not squabble
too early in our partnership.
There'll be plenty of time to
stab each other in the backs later.
But for now, stick to Jerome's plan,
and everyone will get what they want.
An earthly kingdom of terror.
A piece of Gotham
pie both sky and high.
That's the spirit, boys.
Think big. And kinky.
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
And lose the weirdo. She's
giving me the heebie-jeebies.
Your work is done, my
dear. Your race all run.
Glad to be of help.
(CHOKES)
Much better. Now,
to free the rest of our cronies,
and blow this pop stand.
(ALL SHOUTING)
(WHOOPING)
(ALL CHEERING)
Onward, march!
(POLICE SIREN BLARING)
Sure you're up for
this, Captain Gordon?
I'll manage.
Picked a hell of a night
to come back on the job.
- How many got out?
- Eighty-seven.
The entire violent ward.
Yeah, we rounded up
most of the serious nutjobs,
the guys that think they're
walruses and whatnot.
Ephram Snow, child murderer,
Daedalus Boch, mutilator,
Erasmus Rayne,
cult killer... All at large.
The surviving guards think your
old buddy, Tetch, was behind it.
No. This big, this insane,
Jerome Valeska put this together,
and there'll be more to come.
Got a lot of nervous
cops out here tonight
who are thinking
along the same lines.
And I know what you're thinking.
Why not tell them the truth?
About Sofia, and the Pyg,
get it all out in the open.
I've kept my mouth
shut like you told me to.
Good, and I'm telling
you again. Don't slip.
Go over there and be
big Jim Gordon, hero cop.
It's what they need,
even if it is a lie.
MALE OFFICER 1: Hey, Cap.
FEMALE OFFICER: Good to see you, sir.
- Welcome back, Captain.
- Hey, back at it.
MALE OFFICER 2: Hey, Cap. MALE
OFFICER 3: Good to see you, boss.
All right, listen up.
If I'd have known I'd be
seeing your ugly mugs tonight,
I'd have stayed in the hospital.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Jervis Tetch, Jonathan
Crane, Jerome Valeska.
Each of these madmen
has wreaked a different
kind of havoc on our city.
Now they're on the loose, and
presumably working together,
along with several dozen other
garden-variety psychopaths.
Know their MOs, their
associates, their home turf.
Gotham needs you tonight.
Have each other's backs, and
we'll get through this. Let's go.
ALL: Yes, sir.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Captain Gordon.
- Jim, Jim, Jim.
Why so grim, Jim?
Tetch. What do you want?
I'm not playing
any of your games.
No games this time.
Just some maims,
and your own share of blames
if you don't do what I tell you.
To wit, James.
Find your way to Wood
Street and James Way.
Do it, or I'm gonna
kill someone!
In case you had any doubts.
- It's a setup.
- It's also our chance to catch him.
If we can get Tetch, he
can lead us to Valeska.
- I'll put a squad together...
- No.
The force is spread too
thin looking for the escapees.
- Let's go.
- Sure?
You said we had to have
each other's backs tonight, right?
I'm following orders, Captain.
- I had a thought.
- I'll alert the press.
- What if we're hypnotized?
- What?
Stick with me here.
We both listened to
Tetch on the phone.
What if he hypno-ed us
into coming down here alone?
That would be pretty
stupid, wouldn't it?
So, what, we're either idiots, or
we're hypnotized? Good choices.
You did a good job with
the troops back there.
Thanks. This is Whit
Street. Lights out.
What the hell?
We gotta get them out of there.
No, don't shoot,
they're hypnotized!
- They're hypnotized! Don't shoot!
- Back off!
All right, buddy. Come on, hey!
TETCH: Lo and behold,
the bold Captain Jim Gordon,
and his rusty caboose in tow.
You have us, Tetch, let them go.
Do you recall when I first
came to this fair city, Jim?
A bawling mess,
wanting nothing more
than to address the safety
of my dear sister, Alice?
What's the choice
this time, Tetch?
How do I save them?
Just tell me what you want.
What I want is my sister back!
But you kept me from saving her.
You gave me no choice!
So, no more choices for
you, either. No more saving.
(CHAIN RATTLING)
No!
(GRUNTING)
Soon, the bells will toll, Jim.
How many more
will grow cold, Jim?
Like your soul, Jim!
How many would-be
flyers will be die-ers?
Splattered like my
poor spitted Alice.
When the Gotham
bells toll their full roll!
(ALL CLUCKING)
You said you needed
help, but you didn't say
anything about walking
straight into the GCPD.
You wanna bail out now?
No, I just wanna make
sure there's no jewelry debt.
There's no debt.
I helped you to get the jewelry
back because I want to help.
Nobody does
anything just to help.
Fine. Once this is over,
there will be nothing left to
settle between us. Can you do it?
(SCOFFS)
(LOCK RATTLING)
Okay.
(LOCK CLICKS)
Okay, got it. Which file?
Jerome Valeska. There'll
be a red Arkham stamp on it.
Valeska? What do
you want with that nut?
He broke out of Arkham tonight.
Yeah. What does it
have to do with you?
Can you just get the file
before someone sees us?
MAN ON RADIO: The
largest single breach of security
in the troubled history
of Arkham Asylum
has led to a citywide curfew
as many of the worst criminals
who have ever plagued
Gotham flood the streets.
Twenty-seven deaths have
been attributed to the escapees...
The city is going crazy pants.
Can we turn that thing off?
We could be out
there making a killing
while the cops are
rounding up all these nutjobs.
I am gonna go nuts if we
don't turn that damn thing off!
MAN ON RADIO: Please
be aware that these escapees
are extremely dangerous...
(RADIO SWITCHES OFF)
Another migraine?
Nothing a little
self-medication won't fix.
And your hand?
Got a pill for that?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I'll fix it.
I've been reading ancient
history, mysticism, philosophy,
anything that might
reference Ra's al Ghul.
I'm sick of hearing
that charlatan's name.
He brought me back to life.
We've never even
met. Why choose me...
- (HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
- (GROANS)
For all you know,
he lied to you.
Maybe he just told
you, you were dead.
I mean, you can't even
remember what happened.
It hurts to remember.
What?
The attacks I'm having,
it's like memories are trying
to push their way into my brain,
but when I go to touch
them, it's just this searing pain.
- You have to let them in.
- It hurts too much.
Listen to you, whining
like a little baby.
What?
You have been hiding here
for weeks, reading these books.
And now, you're telling
me you might have
all the answers in your head,
but don't want to get them
because it hurts too much?
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
No, I have no idea
who I'm talking to.
The Barbara I know wouldn't
let anything that she's afraid of
stand in the way
of what she wants.
Not cops, not criminals,
not blood, and not pain.
(BARBARA SIGHS)
I remember when
it all went dark.
It was this blinding
electric light,
and then,
nothing.
And then I remember...
(EXHALES)
I remember...
(SCREAMS)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- (GROANS)
RA'S: I know. I hear you.
The world and its cruelties,
how unfair it's been to you.
I can hear you cursing it.
(SIZZLING)
(GASPS)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
What a vital, poisonous
little mind you have.
And yet, everybody
hates you for it, don't they?
Yes.
Everybody hates me.
I don't know why.
I understand that
feeling very well, Barbara.
You are just the one
I've been looking for.
And I have a present
for you. But it's a secret.
You shall become
The Demon's Head.
The League of Shadows
will be yours to command.
An army of assassins.
The world is weak, Barbara.
And you are strong.
Use the League to make the world
more like you.
Barbara?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I'm okay. Ra's just really...
Understood me.
So, you remember something?
Yeah. It's a beacon
calling them here,
- and they're coming.
- Who?
The League of Shadows.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
All right. Hey! Same
story all around.
Last thing they remember
is, they were driving,
and then they were here,
and then it was cluck cluck,
here a chick, there
a chick. Any luck?
Something bad's gonna
happen. And there's a time limit.
That's the Gotham
bells' full roll.
Midnight, right? That's
less than an hour.
What's the bad thing
that's gonna happen?
I don't know. He's gonna
hypnotize more people?
- To do what?
- "Splatted like my spitted Alice."
His sister Alice
jumped, was impaled.
"Flyers will become
die-ers." They'll be splatted.
- Oh, no.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Come on.
(MOUTHING)
Bruce Wayne? What
are you doing here?
Detective Harper.
Where is Captain
Gordon? I need to see him.
He's out on the Arkham
break. What do you need?
(CLATTERING)
I need protection. Last year,
I captured Jerome Valeska.
He's clearly escaped so that
he can get his revenge on me.
Okay, I think it's a
little bit more than that.
I am very close friends
with Captain Gordon.
I'm sure he wants me
to be well-protected,
but if this is a
matter of payment...
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Put that away.
What do you want,
a bribery charge?
I... I just...
I'm sorry, I just... I'm
just really scared. (SOBS)
I know Valeska wants me dead.
- I just know it.
- Take it easy, Wayne.
All right, you can stay
here. You'll be perfectly safe.
Okay.
All right, Wayne.
Let's find you a seat.
Hold on, we're
gonna get you down.
GORDON: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tetch has them booby-trapped.
If we get too close, they'll jump.
But if we do nothing,
they jump at midnight.
How did he get to all of them?
And the drivers, how did
he hypnotize all of them?
What's that matter? We
gotta help these people.
We gotta put a net
around the building.
A net won't work, Harvey.
- Do you know this diner? Zach's?
- No, why?
Look, Valeska's uncle owns it.
He might know where Jerome
would go after escaping.
Still sounds like
a cop's job to me.
I could've killed Jerome after
he kidnapped me, and I didn't.
Any harm he does
now, I share a part of it.
In a way, I'm responsible
for his life now.
I can't just wait to see
what the cops will do.
I have to get him
back to Arkham.
What?
Your ego, Bruce. It's huge.
Not everything is your
fault, or your responsibility.
Get over yourself.
It'll make you a little
easier to be around.
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
Thanks for the advice.
(SELINA CHUCKLES)
You sure you don't
need my help anymore?
- We're even?
- You don't owe me anything, Selina.
You never did.
Are you sure you haven't heard
from your nephew, Mr. Trumble?
That monster killed my
sister. If I ever see him,
his screams are
what you'll be hearing.
Just maybe give us a call
before things go that far.
(DOOR BELL TINKLING)
JEROME: Jeez, there's
a lot of gum under here!
Ah.
You're lucky those flat-foots didn't
check under the table, Uncle Zach.
(GRUNTS)
I mean, it's gotta be some kind of
health code violation or something.
HARVEY: Jim, it's
happening all over the city.
Thousands are climbing up
on roofs, more every minute.
Drivers, people at work,
on the streets, at home.
How's he getting to them?
Radio. He's
broadcasting on radio.
He must have taken
over a radio station.
Which one? We don't
have time to hit them all.
The drivers who grabbed us.
They were listening
to the same station.
(RADIO PLAYING INDISTINCTLY)
GORDON: XTJN here.
HARVEY: WYED.
- WEPV.
- They were all on different stations.
He must have commanded them to change
the station, so we couldn't find him.
There's only one way to
know which one he's using.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no, Harvey.
Harvey, hey! Harvey.
- Hey!
- WYED. Clear.
- Harvey, no, let me go...
- KPIL.
That toilet-paper
jingle I love so much.
I kept Tetch out of my head
once before. I can do it again.
XDNJ!
- (GROANS) It's that song I hate.
- Come on!
(MUSIC PLAYING)
JEROME: Mmm.
Too cold.
Ah! Too hot. Ah!
Oh. Just right.
Mmm.
You always could
cook up a storm, Unc.
I remember back in the circus,
we used to dare each other
to sneak into the chuck wagon
to steal one of your cookies or two.
That reminds me of my
favorite meal you ever cooked.
(TAPS ON TABLE)
You remember that time
you caught me trying
to snag a snickerdoodle?
Oh.
That soup you made that
day. Mmm, mamma mia.
What was the special
ingredient again?
Ah, right. It was my hand.
The one you dipped in a
boiling pot of chicken stock!
That smell, it was...
Mouth-watering.
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
- Almost as good as this. Mmm.
- That's a good story, nephew.
But aren't you curious
about the soup?
- Don't tell me it's poisoned.
- (LAUGHS) Not at all.
Mmm.
You had me worried there for
a second, Unc. (CHUCKLES)
I set out three bowls
of soup, nephew,
so I'd have enough
for all my guests.
- (GROANS)
- (LAUGHS)
You remember Lunkhead from
his strongman days at the circus?
The minute I heard you broke
out, I knew you'd be headed here.
So, I invited good old
Lunk for some supper.
The "just right" soup is
for him, the "cold" is for me.
I always loved
gazpacho! (LAUGHING)
The "too hot," that's
for you, nephew.
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
I'm just saying, how could there
be a global army of assassins
we've never heard of?
What part of "League of
Shadows" do you not understand?
- And they're coming here?
- To me. They're coming to me.
Well, hell, Barb, shouldn't we be
getting ready for them or something?
Oh, I'm ready. As soon as
they wanna show themselves.
What?
You can stop hiding.
(ELECTRICITY SURGING)
I know you're there.
We're here for The Demon's Head.
Where is he?
"She" is right here.
Harvey!
WZPZ.
TETCH ON RADIO: Time to
climb to the tippy-top of every tower.
- When the bell strikes 12:00...
- Jim! WZPZ.
- Pell-mell over the edge...
- Stop listening.
That's an order, you hear me?
Stop listening.
- WZPZ.
- Change the station.
Come on, Harvey,
change the station.
- (RADIO STOPS PLAYING)
- Oh, whoa.
Wait...
Sorry, pal, there's
something I gotta do.
Hickory dickory dock The
cop who went up the clock
The clock struck 12:00
He fell pell-mell And
that was it for the cop.
- HARPER: Gotham Central.
- Harper, it's Gordon.
Cap, it is crazy here. I got
seven cops ready to jump,
I got calls coming
in from everywhere.
It's Tetch, he's broadcasting
from the WZPZ station.
- Okay, I'll redirect units.
- No, I want all cars on the street,
ready to amplify in the
emergency G911 band.
Radio teams on as
many roads as possible.
And then what?
Wait for my signal.
(GRUNTS)
Wait, wait, wait. No, no. No!
(LAUGHS)
Here, nephew. Have a taste
of one of my three soups.
JEROME: No, no, no, no. (GAGS)
My sister had the wrong idea
with you, keeping you around.
She should have put you
in a sack with some rocks
and dropped you in the river!
(COUGHS)
Put this creep
out of our misery.
(GROANS)
- What the hell are you doing?
- Get outta here, kid.
No.
Look, kid, I appreciate a
concerned citizen and all,
but this is Jerome Valeska,
the psycho who broke
out of Arkham tonight.
And what we're doing is
giving him what he deserves.
No one deserves that.
- You tell him...
- Shut up.
BRUCE: Stop.
Call the police, and
they'll come for him.
Aw, jeez, let him go.
And get rid of the kid.
(LAUGHS)
Look what we left lying around.
Enough reliving old
memories, Uncle Zach.
Tell me what I wanna
know. You know why I'm here.
I don't know anything!
It's too bad we're out of soup. I
wonder what else is on the menu.
Ah!
She's got the mark
of The Demon's Head.
- Ra's chose her.
- She doesn't even know what it is.
I know it means I'm
your new damn leader.
Is that all you think it is?
Ra's didn't explain everything.
Look at the mess
he's left us with.
You have the mark
of The Demon's Head,
but no woman has ever been
allowed to lead the League of Shadows.
I'm sorry, you just said what?
Women serve in the
League, but they do not lead.
That's not a law, just a
stupid tradition. Ra's chose her.
We need to honor his choice.
That's true.
As long as you have The Demon's
Head, the League must follow you.
Now, we're back on track.
So, I guess I'll have to cut
The Demon's Head from you.
(GROANS)
Anyone else want
a shot at the title?
- JEROME: Here comes the airplane.
- No, no, no.
No, no, I'll tell
you! I'll tell you.
She picked St. Ignatius!
The school is St. Ignatius!
Got it. Lost it. Write it down.
(BRUCE GRUNTS)
Thanks. It's been great
catching up, Uncle Zach.
You really brought back the
utter helplessness of childhood.
Well, see you around. I
mean, except the opposite.
Boy billionaire Bruce
Wayne, my savior.
Wow, I did not see
that one coming.
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, you know, with Uncle Zach,
the beatings just never stopped.
They went on and on.
And nobody ever helped me.
Ever.
And that makes a man wonder,
what the hell is wrong with you?
(LAUGHING MANICALLY)
The only thing funnier
than you saving my life,
would be if I saved yours.
No!
No. Wait.
What would be funnier
is if you were choked to death
by the guy that you saved me from.
Yeah, yeah, we'll do that
instead. Yeah, yeah, do your thing.
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Almost magic hour, Gothamites.
Time to climb to the
tippy-top of every tower.
When the bell strikes
12:00, throw yourselves,
pell-mell over the
edge, onto your heads!
- (GUN COCKS)
- (GASPS)
Shut up, Tetch.
(RADIO STATIC)
This is Captain
Gordon of the GCPD.
- Am I coming through?
- You're coming through.
They can hear
you all over the city.
All right, Tetch, you're
gonna tell those people
to step back from
the ledge. No tricks.
You go off-script, and
I'll shoot pieces off you
till you do what I say.
I would love to do as
you command, Jim.
But sadly, I've tied my
own hands. (CHUCKLES)
Your hands?
(LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
I can't stop them.
If anyone tells them to
save themselves, they'll jump.
You're more than
welcome to try, Jim.
Obey the next voice you hear!
Tell them anything,
it will not matter when
the bells start to ring.
Your oh-so-callous caused the
death of my darling Alice, Jim.
Try, and they die. Stand
by, and they all try to fly.
(LAUGHS)
Cap?
Cap, what do we do?
How do we save them?
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
I could watch this
all night, Bruce!
(LAUGHING)
Hands off, big boy.
(GRUNTS)
Still don't need my help, Bruce?
Selina.
"Selina," huh? Well,
isn't that a nice name.
(GUN CLICKS)
- Selina.
- No, no, no.
She's not that kind of girl.
- Wrong answer, freak.
- Oh. That's funny, 'cause...
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
(PANTING)
Oh, all right, see
you crazy kids later!
Ciao!
You should've let me shoot him.
Would've been over by now.
Selina, I told you I'm
responsible for him.
I can't just let him be
shot, Selina, I can't.
I'm not taking
responsibility for this mess.
So, let's get out of here
before the cops show up. Yeah?
Come on.
It's not over yet.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
Hey, suit yourself.
Just don't take
so much responsibility,
that you get yourself killed.
(SWORDS CLANKING)
Some legacy your
dead boyfriend left you.
No. Ra's chose me
for a reason. I know it.
(BARBARA GASPS)
You're weak. You're
all so damn weak.
That's it.
That is why Ra's chose me.
Because he knew I would
see how pitiful you all are.
Afraid of change, afraid to
take orders from a woman.
Well, listen up! I am
The Demon's Head!
So, you sons of bitches better
start bowing down right now,
or it's gonna get
ugly up in here.
(RAPID GUN FIRING)
You're right. They were weak.
And the mission of the League
of Shadows is to cull weakness.
They were unfit
and needed to die.
But the sisters of the
League are yours to command.
Well, it's not much
of a league now, is it?
We're the point of
the spear, Barbara.
Hundreds will follow you.
What the hell?
You have no idea what
they expect from you.
This is mine, Tabitha.
And I'm taking it.
Tell me what I need to know.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
(BELL TOLLING)
(SIREN WAILS)
HARPER: Cap, what do we do?
(BELL CONTINUES TOLLING)
I can't save you.
Save each other.
HARPER: It worked.
It worked. They're
stepping away.
- (GASPS)
- What?
I got you. I got you.
(CHEERING)
(SIGHS)
Heard we got nothing from
Tetch about Valeska's plans.
Not a word the whole time the
medics were patching him up.
Still, 40 escapees
back in the can,
and a lot of people with
their feet safely on the ground.
- You need a drink.
- I don't keep it around.
Squirrels hide
nuts for the winter.
I got this for whenever.
I don't belong here. I
don't deserve to be here.
Not in this office,
not in this building.
By rights, I should be in jail.
No argument from me.
But say you were in jail,
sucking on your own misery,
where would the thousands of
people you saved tonight be, huh?
Where would I be?
What you did tonight was heroic.
You could've done what
I did. Anyone could have.
You know what I was thinking
when I jumped in that car
and I was flicking
through those channels?
I was thinking, "I
can do this crazy thing
""cause if it goes sideways,
Jim Gordon will save me."
And here we are.
Who I am,
what I've always said I believe
in, it's like it's a lie now, Harvey.
Feet of clay are
heavy to carry around.
That's what the whiskey's for.
I judged you. For a long time.
I shouldn't have done that.
What you know about me,
Jim, is just the tip of the iceberg.
There are no heroes here.
No heroes here.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Yeah?
Got the Wayne kid on line
three. Something about Valeska.
(DOOR CLOSES)
- GORDON: Bruce, are you okay?
- I saw Jerome Valeska tonight.
- He killed his uncle.
- What?
He was looking for the
name of a school, St. Ignatius.
- Why?
- I'm on my way to find out.
No, wherever you are, stay put.
Valeska is my problem
as much as anyone's.
- I'm going after him.
- Damn it, Bruce.
Stay the hell away
from that madman.
I'll see you at
St. Ignatius, Jim.
- You can yell at me there.
- Bruce...
(LINE DISCONNECTS)
Kid in trouble again?
More than he can
handle. Let's go.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
How do you like the
new threads? Hmm?
Oh, speechless, I know.
(GASPS)
CRANE: You look
a fright, Mr. Tetch.
Somewhat lame,
my dear Mr. Crane.
But I do confess pure joy in
besting Jimmy boy with our ploy.
Yeah, yeah, you did a great
job keeping Gordon occupied,
meanwhile, Crane got his
Fear gas, I got my information.
Everything is going
according to my plan.
But no time to
palaver, gentlemen.
We have fish to fry.
And by "fish," I mean faces.
Or feet.
Ah! Something fun to fry.
Buckle up.
All aboard!
Ooh, I'm coming!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
English - SDH